Guide to the Theobald Wilson photographs 2013.005
Brooklyn Historical Society
Theobald Wilson photographs
1918-2011
1960-2011
Brooklyn Historical Society
Wilson, Theobald
2013.005
11.3 Linear Feet in twenty nine binders and ten boxes
12.58 Gigabytes in 9,790 files
The collection consists of photographs taken by Theobald Wilson, a commercial photographer who was based in Brooklyn, dating from 1918 to 2011. The bulk of the collection is comprised of his commercial photography. The photographs primarily document churches (especially West Indian congregations) and fraternal organizations in the Crown Heights and surrounding neighborhoods of Brooklyn. In addition to the commercial photography, the collection also contains personal photographs, business records, photography equipment, and personal papers relating Wilson and his family.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of photographs taken by Theobald Wilson, a commercial photographer who was based in Brooklyn, dating from 1918 to 2011. The bulk of the collection is comprised of his commercial photography. They primarily consist of photographic negatives (black-and-white and color), although there are some prints and digital images as well. The photographs primarily document churches (especially West Indian congregations) and fraternal organizations in the Crown Heights and surrounding neighborhoods of Brooklyn. In addition to the commercial photography, the collection also contains personal photographs, business records, photography equipment and personal papers relating Wilson and his family.
Biographical note
Theobald G. Wilson was born on January 10, 1923 in the San Juan Hill neighborhood of Manhattan. His mother was a Jamaican immigrant. He had two older sisters, Dorothy and Mavis. Wilson graduated from Dewitt Clinton High School in the Bronx. Before and after World War II he was a resident of the Harlem neighborhood of Brooklyn, where he befriended many political and cultural luminaries, such as Sammy Davis Jr., Percy Sutton, Al Sharpton, Alex Haley, Thelonius Monk, and Gordon Parks. Wilson enlisted in the U.S. Army in 1941 and was invited to join the 99th Pursuit Squadron, which is popularly known as the Tuskegee Airmen. He served in North Africa and Italy as a parachute rigger and took up photography during his service to document his experiences. In the late 1940s he married Marie Dowell and they had two children, Sidney and Susannah. They lived at a number of locations in Manhattan, including 63rd and Amsterdam Avenue and the Amsterdam Houses (1948-1956). They then moved to Brooklyn, residing at 909 Belmont Avenue (1956-1963), 646 Eastern Parkway (1963), Underhill Avenue, Church Avenue and Ocean Avenue, Crown Street, 199 Lincoln Road, and finally 84 Ross Street (Bedford Gardens). Wilson ran a successful commercial photography business out of his home for several decades. His clients included corporations such as AT&T and CBS, as well as numerous churches, fraternal organizations, and other organizations in Brooklyn, especially among West Indian communities. His wife, Marie Wilson, was a well-known quilter, president of the New York Quilter's Society, and was selected to coordinate the "Weaver of Dreams" quilt displayed at the Martin Luther King Jr. Center for Nonviolent Social Change in Atlanta. Theobald was a member of the Church of St. Mark, which is located in the Crown Heights neighborhood of Brooklyn. Marie Wilson passed away in 1997 and Theobald Wilson passed away in 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Sid Wilson and Susan Van Norton, 2013.
Related Archival Materials
The Harry Kalmus papers and photographs (ARC.046) also contains the work of a Brooklyn-based commercial photographer.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into five series:
Series 1: Commercial photographs
Series 2: Business records
Series 3: Personal photographs
Series 4: Personal papers
Series 5: Photography equipment
African Americans |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Bedford-Stuyvesant (New York, N.Y.); Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.); Churches -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Commercial photography; Crown Heights (New York, N.Y.); Day care centers |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Fishing; Fraternal organizations |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Jamaica Bay (N.Y.); Medusa (N.Y.); Outdoor recreation; Photographers |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Prospect Lefferts Gardens (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Quilting; Sheepshead Bay (New York, N.Y.); Veterans |z New York (State) |z Kings County; West Indian Americans |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Artifacts (object genre); Digital Photographs; Negatives (photographic); Photographs; Wilson, Theobald; Church of St. Mark (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Cornerstone Baptist Church (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Independent United Order of Mechanics; Order of Eastern Star. Deborah Grand Chapter of Empire State; Saint Gregory's Roman Catholic Church (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Tuskegee Airmen, Inc. Claude B. Govan Tri-State Chapter
- Series 1: Commercial photographs, 1976-2011; 5.3 Linear Feet in twenty nine binders, twelve folders, five oversize folders, and one oversize print; 12.2 Gigabytes in 9,618 files
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  The series contains photographic negatives (black-and-white and color), prints, and digital images that were created by Wilson for his commercial photography business. The photographs date from 1976 to 2011, with the bulk of the photographs dating from 2001 to 2011. In addition to the photographs, the series also contains some business records relating to the photography shoots and ephemera relating to the organizations that are featured in the photographs (sometimes featuring Wilson's work).
  The photographs predominantly document churches and congregations in the Crown Heights and surrounding neighborhoods of Brooklyn, especially the Church of St. Mark (1417 Union Street), St. Gregory the Great Roman Catholic Church (224 Brooklyn Avenue), and Cornerstone Baptist Church (289 Lewis Avenue), among several others. The photographs document events (such as confirmations and first communions), church groups, and individuals. Notable individuals include Rev. Calvin Bess (Bishop of Trinidad and Tobago), Rev. E. Don Taylor (third bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of the Virgin Islands and assistant bishop in the Episcopal Diocese of New York), and Rev. John Holder (Anglican Archbishop of the West Indies).
  Other subjects include fraternal organizations (Independent United Order of Mechanics, Deborah Grand Chapter of the Empire State), day care centers, schools and alumni events, birthdays and anniversaries, and health care organizations. Wilson was a member of the Tuskegee Airmen, and the series contains photographs of relating to the Claude B. Govan Tri-State Chapter of Tuskegee Airmen, a non-profit organization that promotes the legacy of the airmen and the spirit of aviation and science among young people.
  The series also contains portraits of several notable New York politicians and judges, including David Dinkins, Ed Koch, Percy Sutton, Oliver Sutton, Al Sharpton, Fritz Alexander, Susan D. Johnson Cook, and Robert T. Johnson.
  - Assorted images (portraits, events, etc., many relating to St. Marks Church): Keith Anderson and grandson, Sam Aldrick, Mariette Albert, Eustace Bowen and wife, Alison Beache (People's Cathedral baptism), Canon Leopold Baynes and wife wedding, Borel with nephew, Mrs. Bowen, Jerry Branker, Avis Branker, Veronica Armstrong, Norman and Cedric Arno, Helen Bartow, Anne Batten, Rev. H. Banks, painters and decorators, Caralita Branker and family dance, Rubert Byfield, Judith (Kati) Carrington, Catherwood, Pete Nathaniel Carey (Grandeur Sporting Club), Jocelyn Bryan, H. Bull, Arthur Phipps, Dave's grave, Ruby Brooks, Jocelyn Brian, Ruppert and Norma France, Brotherhood of St. Vincent awarded to Vincent Welsh, Canada Ruppert, Arthur Clarke (organist, choirmaster, Church of St. Mark), Edna Cameroon Branker and family, Leon Chage, Marjorie Clark, Gilbert Clarke (305 Montgomery Street), Ken Dale, R.C. Crossdale group, Valerie Crossdale, Frances Curl family, Leighton Dingwall, Kimberly Davis, Geneva-Watson Dean, Charles Plummer Dickens, Sheila Dash and daughter, James Doyle and family, Major and Laurat Edwards, Margaret Elles, Anzie Frazier, Hilda Glen, Mary Frances, Oswald Francis, Eileen Graham, "Bro" Grant, Flemming family, Avis Gitton (?), Camelia Granderson and family, Anthony Grant backyard and family, Ivy Wilson, Kenneth Grant (Alpha Lodge), Clarene and Betty Griffith, Mattie Grant (Deborah Grand Chapter), Maurice Hamilton, Dorret Headley, Carol Hackett and husband, Valda and Nevil Hollingsworth, Nina Hinds, George Hope (?), Rev. Hinds (St. Mark), Gloria Huntley, Joyce and Malcom Hurley family, Evrith "Jackie" Jackson, Winston Jones (Mechanics Lodge meeting), Winston Jones, Theodore and Milliee Kelley, Alethia Lashley, Theodore Kelly, Penelope Jones, George Kelly, Stanley Johnson (St. Mark), Winston Lewis, Oscar Lobell, Naomi Kerr, Pamela and Desiree Knight, Jerry and Mary King, Robert and Jannette Kirton, Diana Luard (?), John (Elmer) and Louise Morse, Vernice Lundy, Mrs. Padmore, Brother Anthony Michael, Euphenia Nurse, Gwen Owen and husband (Queens College graduation), Jacob "Tyree" Phillips, Cynthia Padmore (St. Mark), Arthur Phillips (organist, St. Mark), Arlene Punnett and family, Lydia Roberts baby christening, John Burns, Charlotte Lewis, Gus Saunders and family, Bishop Richard Martin, Hyacynth Robinson, Frank McGibbons and family, 1976-2007 (Binder 2)
  - Sam Heron, Ophelia and Frank Perry, Michael "Rickey" Sam, Clerist Sargeant family, Ingrid Scrubb (St. Mark), Merle Simpson, Elza and Cheryl Sharp, Pamela Sharp (Queens College graduation), Velma Smith and grandparents, John T. Spring, St. Gregory Philliman - The Sexton, Dorothy Caroson Thomas, Caroson family, Roberta Todd (deacon), Bishop O. Walker, Frank and Joan Walcott and family, Hudson Waldron, Vincent Welch, Joyce Saunders, Winston and Theresa Smith and son, Bishop E. Don Taylor, St. Gregory the Great Roman Catholic Church children, Southeast Queens Environmental Coral Sequence, Dorret Headley, Sam Heron, Carol McNeil fishing permit, Tribune Society, Dr. James, Percy Sutton, Fritz Alexander, David Dinkins, Ed Koch, Suzan Johnson Cook, Rev. Al Sharpton, Robert T. Johnson, 1976-2007 (Binder 29)
  - Harlem Teams Inc. 144 West 138th Street, 175 West 137th Street, 179 West 137th Street. Striver's Row. Cecil Hotel (118th Street at St. Nicholas Avenue), 1979-1981 (Binder 5)
  - M&J Sausage Company - 540 Craven Street, Bronx, 1981/04 (Binder 6)
  - Oliver Sutton, banners, quilt, Christmas card, Apollo Theater, 1982-1983 (Binder 17)
  - Percy E. Sutton, 1981/02/01 (Binder 6)
  - Portraits, 1984/02/01 (Binder 26)
  - Directory of Lawyers. Finley, Kumble, Wagner, Hine, Underberg, Manley, and Caey, 1984/02/22 (Binder 1)
  - Rev. Donaldson and wife, Rev. Noel Foderingham, Rev. Heron A. Sam, Elaine Brahm, Annie Ben, Zita Michaels, Donna Lewis, Denise Washington, Dawn Edwards, Shawn Wint, Gary Hernandez, Clemont Rodney, Pamela Wilson, St. Marks Boys pizza party, 1988 graduation, and St. Marks teachers, 1986-1991 (Binder 8)
  - Cathedral Day School, 1990-2002 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Church of St. Gregory the Great - 75th Anniversary Cornerstone Journal, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Percy E. Sutton, 1993/07/04 (Binder 6)
  - Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, 1995/02/11 (Binder 29)
  - Ordination of nine Catholic priests at St. James, Brooklyn, 1997/06/29 (Binder 21)
  - First mass by Rev. Peter Gopaul at St. Gregory, 1997/06/29 (Binder 21)
  - St. Elizabeth Ann Seton School, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - St. Gregory the Great confirmation groups, 1998-2002 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Putnam Child Development Center, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Berean Missionary Baptist Church, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - St. Gregory the Great - Before and after renovations, 1999-2003 (Oversize OS-6)
  - St. Marks Day School and Church of St. Mark calendars, 1999-2004 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Dee's Safe Haven Learning Center, 2000s (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Deborah Grand Chapter?, circa 2000s (Oversize OS-6)
  - Independent United Order of Mechanics, circa 2000s (Oversize OS-6)
  - St. Gregory the Great panoramas, circa 2000 (Oversize OS-6)
  - Unidentified day care or preschool, circa 2000 (Oversize OS-6)
  - Rev. H. Banks, 2001/07/07 (Binder 29)
  - Alston Jack and son (pan drummer album cover), 2001/08/05 (Binder 6)
  - Alston Jack and son (pan drummer album cover), 2001/08/05 (Disk Digital files)
  - Alston Jack (pan drummer album cover), 2001/08/05 (Oversize OS-6)
  - St. Ignatius, 2001-2004 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Church of St. Mark - Golden Age Club, 2001-2007 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    General note
    Wilson was a member. Includes pictoral directories.
  - Polly Dodge Early Learning Center, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Federation of African American Civil Service Org. Inc. Award Luncheon (Ricardo's, 21-01 24th Avenue, Astoria), 2002/03/22 (Binder 17)
  - Kings County Hospital group - 50 years service reunion, 2002/09/14 (Binder 5)
  - Kings County Hospital group - 50 years service reunion, 2002/09/14 (Disk Digital files)
  - Installation of Fr. Rocco C. Danzi, Pastor of St. Ignatius Roman Catholic Church, 2002/09/21 (Binder 15)
  - Installation of Fr. Rocco C. Danzi, Pastor of St. Ignatius Roman Catholic Church, 2002/09/21 (Disk Digital files)
  - St. Gregory the Great postcards, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - The Women's League of Science and Medicine 43rd Annual Luncheon, 2003/03/15 (Binder 15)
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church Business and Professional Women awards luncheon, 2003/09/22 (Binder 7)
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church Business and Professional Women awards luncheon, 2003/09/22 (Disk Digital files)
  - National Council of Negro Women 19th Harambee Breakfast Awards, 2004/04/14 (Binder 8)
  - Church of St. Mark. Trinidad and Tobago Association. Rt. Rev. Calvin Bess, Bishop of Trinidad and Tobago, 2004/04/26 (Binder 1)
  - Sanctified Learning Center, 2004/06/11 (Binder 7)
  - Fr. Gary Philip J. Rogers 25th Anniversary at St. Gregory the Great Roman Catholic Church, 2004/06/20 (Binder 20)
  - Bishop E. Don Taylor, 2004/06/30 (Binder 1)
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church Business and Professional Women's luncheon (Fleur de Lis, 870 Cypress Avenue), 2004/07/28 (Binder 9)
  - Golden Age Club at St. Marks' Award's Luncheon, 2004/07/30 (Binder 20)
  - Bishops' High school Alumni Association 15th Anniversary (St. Mark), 2004/09/26 (Binder 20)
  - Church Women United Rewards Luncheon, 2004/10/23 (Binder 3)
  - Most Worshipful Grand Master Christmas Party (65 Putnam Avenue), 2004/12/05 (Binder 23)
  - Women's League of Science & Medicine Scholarship/Luncheon (Antun's, 96-43 Springfield Boulevard, Queens Village), 2005/03/19 (Binder 20)
  - Loyal Moses Lodge #7 (65 Putnam Avenue), 2005/03/20 (Binder 23)
  - Federation of African American Civil Service Org. Inc. Awards Luncheon, 2005/03/26 (Binder 18)
  - Mechanic's Lodge Executive Grand Council (65 Putnam Avenue), 2005/04/30 (Binder 13)
  - Mechanic's Lodge Executive Grand Council (65 Putnam Avenue), 2005/04/30 (Disk Digital files)
  - St. Ignatius R.C. Church (267 Rogers Avenue) Confirmation and First Holy Communion, 2005/05 (Binder 14)
  - St. Gregory The Great R.C. Church - First Holy Communion, 2005/05/22 (Binder 12)
  - Jesus the Good Shepherd United Reform Episcopal Church - George Irving 94th birthday and service, 2005/06/05 (Binder 20)
  - St. Mary's Grand Council Encampment, 2005/06/05 (Binder 23)
  - Tuscan Chapter, 2005/06/25 (Binder 13)
  - Dedication of Plagues, Tree of Life, Stain Glass Window, Condemnation of Ashes, 2005/08 (Binder 4)
  - Independent United Order of Mechanics, W.H. Inc. Resource and Finance Commission Mechanics 2005 Dinner Dance & Raffle (Grand Prospect Hall), 2005/09/09 (Binder 16)
  - Unidentified church, 2005/10 (Binder 14)
  - Sanctified Learning Center, 2005/10/06 (Binder 16)
  - Carlos Precod and Rev. Denzil Hinds, 2005/11/21 (Binder 5)
  - Carlos Precod and Rev. Denzil Hinds, 2005/11/21 (Disk Digital files)
  - Panama Canal Alumni Association Award Service, 2005/12/06 (Binder 6)
  - St. Gregory First Holy Communion, 2006 (Binder 17)
  - Independent United Order of Mechanics Installation Ceremony and Banquet (65 Putnam Avenue), 2006/01/15 (Binder 24)
  - Unidentified church, 2006/01/25 (Binder 24)
  - Ordination of Deacon Reginal F. Jackson, 2006/02/06 (Binder 14)
  - Brotherhood St. Andrew, Corporate Breakfast, 2006/02/20 (Binder 4)
  - Brotherhood St. Andrew, Corporate Breakfast, 2006/02/20 (Disk Digital files)
  - Tuskegee Airmen Honoring Women's Achievements, 2006/03/19 (Binder 16)
  - Nesititi Order, United Grand Chapter, Royal Ladies, Hiram Temple, 2006/03-04 (Binder 14)
  - Nesititi Order, United Grand Chapter, Royal Ladies, Hiram Temple, 2006/03-04 (Disk Digital files)
  - NAACP Brooklyn Awards, 2006/04/05 (Binder 22)
  - NAACP Brooklyn Awards, 2006/04/05 (Disk Digital files)
  - Benjamin and Rebecca Gabriel 50th wedding anniversary (Fleur de Lis, 870 Cypress Avenue), 2006/04/08 (Binder 19)
  - Church of St. Mark, 2006/04/23 (Binder 24)
  - St. Ignatius First Holy Communion and Confirmation, 2006/05 (Binder 18)
  - The Concord Baptist Church Faithful Servant Awards Luncheon, 2006/05/10 (Binder 8)
  - Unidentified church, 2006/06/04 (Binder 26)
  - Sanctified Church of God Convention (Sanctified Learning Center, 404 Lefferts Avenue), 2006/06/18 (Binder 22)
  - Sanctified Church of God Convention (Sanctified Learning Center, 404 Lefferts Avenue), 2006/06/18 (Disk Digital files)
  - Beth Israel Medical Center - Department of Family Medicine, 2006/07/19 (Binder 17)
  - Eagle Scout Awards at St. Mark (Brando Borel promotion), 2006/07/22 (Binder 12)
  - Jesus the Good Shepherd United Reform Episcopal Church - Mother's Day Recognition, 2006/08/05 (Binder 20)
  - Wilbert Boyce and Jewel Jackson Wedding, 2006/08/10 (Binder 15)
  - Unidentified woman, 2006/09 (Binder 23)
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church Business and Professional Women awards luncheon, 2006/09/23 (Binder 7)
  - Independent Mechanic's Ball (Grand Council Mechanics) (Le Cordon Bleu, 9601 Jamaica Avenue), 2006/10/20 (Binder 12)
  - Independent Mechanic's Ball (Grand Council Mechanics) (Le Cordon Bleu, 9601 Jamaica Avenue), 2006/10/20 (Disk Digital files)
  - George Hope 80th birthday, 2006/10/28 (Binder 19)
  - George Hope 80th birthday, 2006/10/28 (Disk Digital files)
  - Church Women United Awards Luncheon, 2006/10/28 (Binder 19)
  - Church Women United Awards Luncheon, 2006/10/28 (Disk Digital files)
  - Ambrosia Irving 90th Birthday, 2006/11/05 (Binder 13)
  - Ambrosia Irving 90th Birthday, 2006/11/05 (Disk Digital files)
  - Lorretta "Sister" Williams 80th birthday, 2006/11/18 (Binder 4)
  - Lorretta "Sister" Williams 80th birthday, 2006/11/18 (Disk Digital files)
  - Deborah Grand Chapter?, 2006/12/09 (Binder 7)
  - Deborah Grand Chapter?, 2006/12/09 (Disk Digital files)
  - The Chosen Remnant at Emmanuel Baptist Church, 2006/12/20 (Binder 23)
  - The Chosen Remnant at Emmanuel Baptist Church, 2006/12/20 (Disk Digital files)
  - Good Shepherd Church - Consecration of new building (599 Washington Avenue), 2006/12/31 (Binder 13)
  - Good Shepherd Church - Consecration of new building (599 Washington Avenue), 2006/12/31 (Disk Digital files)
  - Monte and Margaret Burke 50th Wedding Anniversary (87 Lefferts Avenue), 2007/01/04 (Binder 23)
  - Monte and Margaret Burke 50th Wedding Anniversary (87 Lefferts Avenue), 2007/01/04 (Disk Digital files)
  - Queen Esther (Deborah Grand Chapter?), 2007/01/07 (Binder 7)
  - St. Marks Youth Enrichment c/o Carlos Prescad, St. Marks Choir c/o Dr. Clarke, 2007/01/29 (Binder 8)
  - St. Marks Youth Enrichment c/o Carlos Prescad, St. Marks Choir c/o Dr. Clarke, 2007/01/29 (Disk Digital files)
  - Dee's Safe Haven Day Care (1656 Sterling Place), 2007/03/08 (Binder 18)
  - Woman's League of Science and Medicine luncheon/awards, 2007/03/17 (Binder 13)
  - Concord Baptist Faithful Servant Awards Luncheon (833 Marcy Avenue), 2007/03/17 (Binder 20)
  - Deborah's Queen Esther pageant, 2007/03/25 (Binder 7)
  - Deborah's Queen Esther pageant, 2007/03/25 (Disk Digital files)
  - Sanctified Learning Center, 2007/04/19 (Binder 23)
  - St. Gregory the Great Roman Catholic Church - First Holy Communion, 2007/06/03 (Binder 25)
  - Tuscon Chapter #11, 2007/06/09 (Binder 25)
  - Empire State Advisory Council, 2007/06/11 (Binder 25)
  - Empire State Advisory Council, 2007/06/11 (Disk Digital files)
  - Sanctified 17th Anniversary/Convention, 2007/06/17 (Binder 25)
  - New York Medical College Family Practice Residency Program, 2007/06/22 (Binder 25)
  - New York Medical College Family Practice Residency Program, 2007/06/22 (Disk Digital files)
  - Beth Israel Medical Center Department of Family Health, 2007/06/27 (Binder 25)
  - Beth Israel Medical Center Department of Family Health, 2007/06/27 (Disk Digital files)
  - Dee's Safe Haven Learning Center, 2007/10/15 (Binder 25)
  - Sanctified Learning Center with NY Councilman, 2007/10/21 (Binder 7)
  - 100th Birthday c/o Everlyn Moore, 2007/10/21 (Binder 7)
  - Church Women United Rewards Luncheon, 2007/10/27 (Binder 3)
  - Church Women United Rewards Luncheon, 2007/10/27 (Disk Digital files)
  - Deborah Grand Chapter with groups and Queen Esther, 2008/01/06 (Binder 1)
  - Deborah Grand Chapter with groups and Queen Esther, 2008/01/06 (Disk Digital files)
  - St. Gregory Confirmation and Communion, 2008/04/06 (Binder 10)
  - Ms. Sylvia Whiskey Virginia Club Awards (First Baptist Church of Crown Heights), 2008/04/12 (Binder 10)
  - Ms. Sylvia Whiskey Virginia Club Awards (First Baptist Church of Crown Heights), 2008/04/12 (Disk Digital files)
  - United Grand Chapter OES Inc., 2008/04/17 (Binder 26)
  - Independent United Order of Mechanics, 2008/04/22 (Binder 12)
  - Independent United Order of Mechanics, 2008/04/22 (Disk Digital files)
  - Dale and Susan Edwards 25th (Silver) wedding anniversary, 2008/05/03 (Binder 12)
  - Dale and Susan Edwards 25th (Silver) wedding anniversary, 2008/05/03 (Disk Digital files)
  - Joan Sam 75th birthday, 2008/05/11 (Binder 7)
  - Tuskegee Airmen NY Chapter, 2008/05/17 (Binder 18)
  - Nick and Kathie Shaw's Fish Fry, 2008/05/25 (Binder 11)
  - Nick and Kathie Shaw's Fish Fry, 2008/05/25 (Disk Digital files)
  - Lewis Memorial Gospel Concert, 2008/06/01 (Binder 9)
  - Lewis Memorial Gospel Concert, 2008/06/01 (Disk Digital files)
  - M+M Barbnan Mollineua + Graduate, 2008/06/11 (Binder 11)
  - M+M Barbnan Mollineua + Graduate, 2008/06/11 (Disk Digital files)
  - St. Marks Africa Club June Teenth Awards, 2008/06/22 (Binder 11)
  - St. Marks Africa Club June Teenth Awards, 2008/06/22 (Disk Digital files)
  - Bobby and Janet K. 50th Wedding Anniversary, 2008/06/22 (Binder 26)
  - Bobby and Janet K. 50th Wedding Anniversary, 2008/06/22 (Disk Digital files)
  - Ms. Brenda Martin graduation (907 Greene Avenue), 2008/07/30 (Binder 26)
  - Ms. Brenda Martin graduation (907 Greene Avenue), 2008/07/30 (Disk Digital files)
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church Business and Professional Women awards luncheon, 2008/09/27 (Binder 26)
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church Business and Professional Women awards luncheon, 2008/09/27 (Disk Digital files)
  - St. Mark Mothers Union, 2008/09/28 (Binder 26)
  - St. Mark Mothers Union, 2008/09/28 (Disk Digital files)
  - Church Women United, 2008/10/25 (Binder 3)
  - Church Women United, 2008/10/25 (Disk Digital files)
  - St. Michael's Priests, 2008/11/06 (Binder 26)
  - St. Michael's Priests, 2008/11/06 (Disk Digital files)
  - Church of the Master, 2008/11/11 (Binder 7)
  - Church of the Master, 2008/11/11 (Disk Digital files)
  - Sanctified Learning Center, 2009/01/16 (Binder 9)